Guide to the Ambassador Auditorium Collection ARS.0043
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Series 10: Concert Recordings, 252 boxes (266.2 linear ft.)
  - Audio Open Reel Tapes and Cassettes
    - Concert Recordings 8506-8515:, 02-11-1985 -- 03-14-1985; 19 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 536)
      (8507:1-2) Dame Janet Baker, mezzo-soprano; Martin Isepp, piano, 02-17-1985: [see also Tapes (8507:1-2), Box 503] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Vado ma dove? oh Dei! -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Al desio, di chi t’adora -- Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Scherzi musicali (1632). Quel sguardo sdegnosetto -- Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Si dolce è’l tormento -- Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603? Ayres. It was a lover and his lasse -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Semele. Where’er you walk -- Cavalli, Pier Francesco, 1602-1676. [Title from program:] Orimonte. Numi ciechi piu di me -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Musensohn -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia -- Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Lieder und Gesänge aus der Jugendzeit. Frühlingsmorgen -- Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Lieder und Gesänge aus der Jugendzeit. Nicht wiedersehen -- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Gesänge, op. 34. Auf Flügeln des Gesanges -- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Gesänge, op. 8. Andres Maienlied -- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Poems of Emily Dickinson. Why do they shut me out of heaven? -- Ives, Charles, 1874-1954. [Title from program:] In summer fields -- Pasatieri, Thomas. [Title from program:] Vocal modesty -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Berenice che fai -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Sérénade -- Lark in the clear air -- Parry, C. Hubert H. (Charles Hubert Hastings), 1848-1918. English lyrics, set 10. My heart is like a singing bird
      (8508:1-2) Fitzwilliam String Quartet, 02-21-1985: [see also Tapes (8508:1-2), Box 503] Shostakovich, Dmitriĭ Dmitrievich, 1906-1975. Quartets, strings, no. 1, op. 49, C major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Quartets, strings, no. 16, op. 135, F major -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Quartets, strings, no. 3, op. 30, E♭ minor
      (8509:1-2) Thomas Hampson, baritone; Armen Guzelimian, piano, Gold Medal Vocal Series, 02-25-1985: [see also Tapes (8509:1-2), Box 503] Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Canzonettas, voice, piano, 2nd set. Sailor’s song -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Canzonettas, voice, piano, 2nd set. Wanderer -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Canzonettas, voice, piano, 2nd set. She never told her love -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Acide e Galatea. Tergi i vezzosi rai -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Don Quichotte à Dulcinée -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Schlichte Weisen. Ach, weh mir unglückhaftem Mann -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 36. Rosenband -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 10. Nichts -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 27. Heimliche Aufforderung -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 29. Traum durch die Dämmerung -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 27. Cäcilie -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Songs, op. 10 -- Bowles, Paul, 1910-1999. Blue Mountain ballads -- Duke, John, 1899-1984. Poems by Edward Arlington Robinson. Richard Cory -- Bowles, Paul, 1910-1999. Once a lady was here -- Ives, Charles, 1874-1954. Memories -- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Old American songs, set 1. Boatmen’s dance -- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Old American songs, set 1. I bought me a cat -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Porter, Cole, 1891-1964. [Title from listing on container:] Goodbye, little dream, goodbye -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive -- Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen
      (8510:1-2) The Deller Consort; Mark Deller, director/countertenor, 02-26-1985: [see also Tapes (8510:1-2), Box 503] Greaves, Thomas, fl. 1604. Songes of sundrie kindes. Come away, sweet love -- Tomkins, Thomas, 1572-1656. Songs, voices (3-6). Too much I once lamented -- Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603? [Title from program:] You that wont to my pipes sound -- [Change in program from listing on container:] Wilbye, John, 1574-1638. Madrigals, voices (3-6), set 2. Weepe, mine eyes -- Cutting, Francis. [Title from program:] Galliard -- Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603? Balletts. Sing wee and chaunt it -- Gibbons, Orlando, 1583-1625. Madrigals and mottets. Silver swanne -- East, Michael, ca. 1580-1648. Bookes, 3rd set. Poor is the life -- Planson, Jean, ca. 1558-ca. 1615. Airs, voices (4). Rousée du joly mois de may -- Bartlet, John, fl. 1606-1610. [Title from program:] When from my love -- Guédron, Pierre, ca. 1565-ca. 1621. [Title from program:] Aux plaisirs, aux delices, bergeres -- Vallet, Nicolas, ca. 1583-ca. 1642. Lute music. [Title from program:] Pantaloons -- Guédron, Pierre, ca. 1565-ca. 1621. [Title from program:] Adorable princesse -- Dowland, John, 1563?-1626. Songs or ayres, 3rd book. What if I never speede -- Le Jeune, Claude, d. 1600. Printemps. Revecy venir du printans -- Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Madrigals, book 8. Dolcissimo uscignolo -- Gesualdo, Carlo, principe di Venosa, 1560 (ca.)-1613. Madrigals, voices (5), book 4. Luci serene e chiare -- Ferrabosco, Alfonso, 1543-1588. [Title from program:] Pavana -- Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Scherzi musicali (1632). Quel sguardo sdegnosetto -- Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Madrigals, book 4. Piagne e sospira -- [Change in program from listing on container:] Name and title unknown -- Dance to your daddy -- Oak and the ash -- Wraggle taggle gypsies -- Greensleeves -- Ca’ the yowes -- Yarmouth fair -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Water of Tyne -- Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603? Balletts. Now is the month of maying
      (8511:1-2) Jessye Norman, soprano; Joseph Villa, piano, 03-03-1985: [see also Tapes (8511:1-2), Box 503] Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Ode for St. Cecilia’s Day. [Title from program:] Wie hebt und senkt Musik der Seele Flug -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Rinaldo. Lascia ch’io pianga mia cruda sorte -- Dank sei dir Herr -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Radamisto, HWV 12a. [Title from program:] Sommi Dei -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Rastlose Liebe -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Auf dem See -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Im Abendrot -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Tod und das Mädchen (Song) -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Erlkönig -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder, op. 106. Ständchen -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder, op. 95. Jäger -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Gesänge, op. 6. Spanisches Lied -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder und Gesänge, op. 58. O komme, holde Sommernacht -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Songs, op. 13. Sure on this shining night -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Songs, op. 18. Monks and raisins -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Songs, op. 13. Nocturne -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Hermit songs. [Title from program:] Praises of God -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Wir beide wollen springen -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 10. Zueignung -- Satie, Erik, 1866-1925. Je te veux -- Bonds, Margaret. He’s got the whole world in his hands -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Samson et Dalila. Mon cœur s’ouvre à ta voix
      (8512:1-2) Colorado String Quartet, Gold Medal String Series, 03-04-1985: [see also Tapes (8512:1-2), Box 504] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Quartets, strings, K. 465, C major -- Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945. Quartets, strings, no. 2, op. 17 -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Quartets, strings, no. 15, op. 132, A minor
      (8513:1-2) The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra of London; Yehudi Menuhin, conductor; Leland Chen, violin, 03-07-1985: [see also Tapes (8513:1-2), Box 504] Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Guillaume Tell. Ouverture -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Concertos, violin, orchestra, op. 35, D major -- [Encore before intermission, from program listing on container:] Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. [unspecified] Sonata in A Minor -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Symphonies, no. 1, op. 68, C minor -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Ungarische Tänze. [number unspecified] G Minor -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Moments musicaux [number unspecified] -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Slovanské tance, op. 46. No. 1
      (8514:1-2) Amadeus Quartet, 03-12-1985: [see also Tapes (8514:1-2), Box 504] Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Quartets, strings, H. III, 77, C major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Quartets, strings, K. 575, D major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Quartets, strings, no. 9, op. 59, no. 3, C major
      (8515:1) Mozarteum Orchestra of Salzburg; Hans Graf, director/conductor; Homero Francesch, piano, 03-14-1985: [see program listing after Tape 8515:2, Box 537]
      Graf, Hans; Royal Philharmonic Orchestra; Francesch, Homero; Colorado Quartet; Menuhin, Yehudi, 1916-1999; Mozarteum-Orchester; Chen, Leland; Amadeus String Quartet; Villa, Joseph; Deller, Mark; Guzelimian, Armen; Isepp, Martin; Lewis, Daniel; Hewgill, Catherine; USC Symphony Orchestra; Baker, Janet; Fitzwilliam String Quartet; Hampson, Thomas; Deller Consort; Norman, Jessye
    - Concert Recordings 8515-8524:, 03-14-1985 -- 04-18-1985; 19 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 537)
      (8515:2) Mozarteum Orchestra of Salzburg; Hans Graf, director/conductor; Homero Francesch, piano, 03-14-1985: [see also Tapes (8515:1-2), Box 504] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Divertimenti, K. 136, D major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 466, D minor -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Symphonies, K. 504, D major -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Marches, orchestra, K. 335. No. 2 -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Deutsche Tänze, orchestra, K. 600
      (8516:1-2) The Cambridge Buskers; Michael Copley, flute and assorted winds; Dag Ingram, accordion, 03-17-1985: [see also Tapes (8516:1-2), Box 504] [From program listing on container:] Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Quintets, piano, violin, viola, violoncello, double bass, D. 667, A major; arr. -- Khachaturi︠a︡n, Aram Ilʹich, 1903-1978. Gai︠a︡nė. Tanet︠s︡ s sabli︠a︡mi; arr. -- Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932. Stars and stripes forever; arr. -- Sailor’s hornpipe medley -- Bach, Johann Christian, 1735-1782. [unspecified] Andantino -- Christmas carol -- Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Cimento dell’armonia e dell’inventione. N. 1; arr. -- Irish Jig, in two parts -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. [Title from container listing:] Dying swan -- [Two unspecified traditional Roumanian pieces] -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Toccatas, organ, BWV 565, D minor; arr. -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 6; arr. -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Symphonies, D. 759, B minor; arr. -- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Concertos, violin, orchestra, op. 64, E minor. Allegro molto vivace; arr. -- [Name and title from container listing:] Morree. Fanfare -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Messiah. Hallelujah; arr. -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. [unspecified] -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Symphonies, H. I, 94, G major; arr. -- Ketèlbey, Albert W. (Albert William), 1875-1959. In a Persian market -- Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Cimento dell’armonia e dell’inventione. N. 4; arr. -- Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Vesna svi︠a︡shchennai︠a︡ -- Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Skazka o t︠s︡are Saltane. Nu, teperʹ, moĭ shmelʹ -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Shchelkunchik. Chaĭ -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Konzertsatz, horn, orchestra, K. [unspecified]. Finale -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. [Title from container listing:] Symphonic third movement medley -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 9, op. 125, D minor. Presto. Allegro assai; arr. -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Donna è mobile -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Walkürenritt; arr. -- Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007. Tierkreis. [Title from container listing:] Capricorn -- Chopsticks (Children’s tune) -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. [Title from container listing:] First piano accordion concerto -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. Vogelfänger bin ich ja -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. 1812 année; arr. -- [Encore, unspecified]
      (8517:1-2) James Barbagallo, Gold Medal Piano Series, 03-18-1985: [see also Tapes (8517:1-2), Boxes 504-505] Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Französische Suiten. Nr. 3 -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Davidsbündlertänze -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Miroirs. Oiseaux tristes -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Miroirs. Alborada del gracioso -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Sonatas, piano, no. 2, op. 14, D minor
      (8518:1-2) Academy of Ancient Music; Christopher Hogwood, director/harpsichord; Emma Kirkby, soprano; David Thomas, bass; Catherine Mackintosh, violin; Christopher Hirons, violin, 03-21-1985: [see also Tapes (8518:1-2), Box 505] Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1068, D major -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Weichet nur, betrübte Schatten -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich habe genug -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, violins (2), string orchestra, BWV 1043, D minor
      (8519:1-2) Kathleen Battle, soprano; Lawrence Skrobacs, piano, 03-23-1985: [see also Tapes (8519:1-2), Box 505] Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Semele. Oh sleep, oh sleep, why dost thou leave me? -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Semele. Endless pleasure, endless love (Air) -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Alcina. Tornami a vagheggiar -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Veilchen -- Mysliveček, Josef, 1737-1781. Caro mio bene; arr. -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Moto di gioia mi sento -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Alinde -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Gott im Frühlinge -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An die Laute -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Szenen aus dem Schauspiel Lacrimas. Lied der Delphine -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 68. An die Nacht -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 68. Ich wollt ein Sträusslein binden -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 68. Säusle, liebe Myrte! -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 68. Als mir dein Lied erklang -- Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Canciones populares españolas. Canción -- Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Canciones populares españolas. Nana -- Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Canciones populares españolas. Seguidilla murciana -- Hayes, Roland, 1887-1977. Plenty good room; arr. -- Work, John W. (John Wesley), 1901-1967. This little light of mine; arr. -- Johnson, Hall, 1888-1970. His name so sweet; arr. -- Gabriel, Chas. H. (Charles Hutchinson), 1856-1932. His eye is on the sparrow; arr. -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Johnson, Hall, 1888-1970. Witness; arr. -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Obéissons quand leur voix appelle -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Mélodies de Venise. Mandoline -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Joshua. Oh had I Jubal’s lyre -- Bonds, Margaret. He’s got the whole world in his hands; arr.
      (8520:1-2) Sergio and Odair Assad, duo-guitarists, 03-31-1985: [see also Tapes (8520:1-2), Box 505] [Change in program, from listing on container; unknown piece consisting of four movements] -- Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, 1895-1968. [Title from program:] Prelude and fugue, No. 1 -- Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, 1895-1968. [Title from program:] Prelude and fugue, No. 17 -- Sor, Fernando, 1778-1839. Fantaisies, guitars (2), op. 54 bis, E major -- Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Selections; arr. -- Gnattali, Radamés, 1906-1988. Brasiliana, no. 8 -- Albéniz, Isaac, 1860-1909. Iberia. Evocación -- Petit, Pierre, 1922-2000. Toccata, guitars (2) -- Piazzolla, Astor. Tango suite -- [Encores, name and title from program listing on container:] Assad. Two Brazilian dances
      (8521:1-2) Viktoria Mullova, violin; Armen Guzelimian, piano, 04-14-1985: [see also Tapes (8521:1-2), Box 505] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, violin, piano, K. 378, B♭ major -- Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945. Sonatas, violin -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 78, G major -- Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840. Concertos, violin, orchestra, no. 2, op. 7, B minor. Rondò
      (8522:1-2) Chantal Juillet, violin, Francine Kay, piano, Gold Medal String Series, 04-15-1985: [see also Tapes (8522:1-2), Box 505] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, violin, piano, K. 454, B♭ major -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 13, A major -- Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945. Sonatas, violin -- Ysaÿe, Eugène, 1858-1931. Sonatas, violin, op. 27. No. 6 -- Wieniawski, Henri, 1835-1880. Polonaise brillante, no. 1; arr. -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. [unspecified] Melody transcribed by Chryzler [Kreisler?]
      (8523:1-2) Narciso Yepes, guitar; Nicanor Zabaleta, harp, 04-17-1985: [see also Tapes (8523:1-2), Box 506] Soler, Antonio, 1729-1783. Concertos, organs (2). No. 3; arr. -- Hovhaness, Alan, 1911-2000. Spirit of trees -- Montsalvatge, Xavier, 1912-2002. Fantasia, guitar, harp [West Coast premiere] -- Rodrigo, Joaquín. [Title from program:] Villano -- Rodrigo, Joaquín. [Title from program:] Espanoleta and Fanfare -- Rodrigo, Joaquín. Fantasía para un gentilhombre. [Title from program:] Canarios -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Turina, Joaquín, 1882-1949. Bailete. Fandango -- Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767. [unspecified] Menuetto
      (8524:1-2) Suk Trio; Josef Suk, violin; Josef Chuchro, cello; Josef Hála, piano, 04-18-1985: [see also Tapes (8524:1-2), Box 506] Suk, Josef, 1874-1935. Elegy, violin, violoncello, instrumental ensemble, op. 23 -- Smetana, Bedřich, 1824-1884. Trio, piano, strings, op. 15, G minor -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Trios, piano, strings, op. 90, E minor -- [Encores, from program listing on container:] Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. [unspecified] Allegro -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. [unspecified] Adagio
      Suk, Josef; Kay, Francine; Chuchro, Josef; Hála, Josef; Hirons, Christopher; Copley, Michael; Thomas, David; Mackintosh, Catherine; Hogwood, Christopher; Kirkby, Emma; Guzelimian, Armen; Skrobacs, Lawrence; Assad, Odair; Assad, Sérgio; Mullova, Viktorii︠a︡; Sukovo trio; Juillet, Chantal; Yepes, Narciso; Ingram, Dag; Francesch, Homero; Graf, Hans; Mozarteum-Orchester; Zabaleta, Nicanor; Cambridge Buskers; Barbagallo, James; Academy of Ancient Music (1973- ); Battle, Kathleen
    - Concert Recordings 8525-8535:, 04-22-1985 -- 06-04-1985; 19 10 1/2" open reel tapes (Box 538)
      (8525:1-2) Mitsuko Uchida, Gold Medal Piano Series, 04-22-1985: [see also Tapes (8525:1-2), Box 506] Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Englische Suiten. Nr. 2 -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, piano, K. 284, D major -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Sonatas, piano, D. 894, G major -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, [unspecified] D minor
      (8526:1-2) Andre Watts, piano, 04-25-1985: [see also Tapes (8526:1-2), Box 506] Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Variations, piano, WoO 80, C minor -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 13-14, op. 27 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Nocturnes, piano, op. 48. No. 1 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Fantaisies, piano, op. 49, F minor -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 10. No. 1 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 10. No. 12 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 25. No. 1 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 10. No. 9 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 25. No. 7 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Etudes, piano, op. 10. No. 4 [Encores, from program listing on container:] Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas [unspecified] -- Tcherepnine, Nicolas, 1873-1945. [unspecified] Bagatelle -- Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Preludes, piano [unspecified]
      (8527:1-2) Elmar Oliveira, violin; Robert McDonald, piano, 04-28-1985: [see also Tapes (8527:1-2), Box 506] Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 3, op. 12, no. 3, E♭ major -- Respighi, Ottorino, 1879-1936. Sonatas, violin, piano, B minor -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Romantické kusy -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Sonatas, flute, piano, op. 94, D major; arr. -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Kreisler, Fritz, 1875-1962. [Title from listing on container:] Chanson indienne
      (8529:1-2) American Youth Symphony, Gold Medal Orchestra Series; Mehli Mehta, director/conductor; Timothy Landauer, cello, 05-06-1985: [see also Tapes (8529:1-2), Boxes 506-507] Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Zauberharfe. Ouvertüre -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Concertos, violoncello, orchestra, no. 1, op. 33, A minor -- Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840. Sonata a preghiera -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 3, op. 55, E♭ major
      (8530:1-2) Malcolm Bilson, fortepiano, 05-09-1985: [see also Tapes (8530:1-2), Box 507] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, piano, K. 570, B♭ major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 17, op. 31, no. 2, D minor -- Cramer, J. B. (Johann Baptist), 1771-1858. Variations sur l’air Ein Mädchen oder Weibchen -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Adagios, piano, K. 540, B minor -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Gigues, piano, K. 574, G major -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Sonatas, piano, H. XVI, 52, E♭ major -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, piano, K. 281, B♭ major. [From listing on container: second movement] Andante amoroso
      (8531:1-2) Pasadena Unified School District All City Instrumental Music Festival, 05-15-1985: Elementary All City Honor Orchestra -- Junior High School Honor String Orchestra -- Junior High School All City Honor Band -- Senior High School Honor Orchestra [see program in container for more information]
      (8532:1-2) Sherry Kloss, violin, Gold Medal String Series; Brooks Smith, piano, 05-20-1985: [see also Tapes (8532:1-2), Box 507] Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 7, op. 30, no. 2, C minor -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Sonatas, violin, piano, op. 18, E♭ major -- Scott, Cyril, 1879-1970. Tallahassee suite -- Badings, Henk, 1907-1987. Capriccios, violin, tape -- Hubay, Jenő, 1858-1937. Blumenleben. Zephyr -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Zigeunermelodien. Als die alte Mutter; arr. -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum; arr. -- [Encore, from program listing on container:] Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Stimmungsbilder. An einsamer Quelle
      (8533:[1 unnumbered reel]) Pasadena Youth Symphony Orchestra Spring Concert; Donn Laurence Mills, conductor, 05-23-1985: [see also Tape (8533:1), Box 507] Cacavas, John. [Title from program:] Time of kings -- Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Shekherazada. Andantino quasi allegretto; arr. -- Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869. Symphonie fantastique. Marche au supplice; arr. -- Kuhlau, Friedrich, 1786-1832. Duets, flutes, op. 39. No. 1 -- Dvořák, Antonín, 1841-1904. Symphonies, no. 8, op. 88, G major. Allegro ma non troppo; arr. -- Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907. Lyriske stykker, op. 65. Bryllupsdag på Troldhaugen; arr. -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Divertimenti, K. 213, F major; arr. -- Lalo, Edouard, 1823-1892. Symphonie espagnole. Allegro non troppo -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Symphonies, D. 944, C major; arr. -- Benjamin, Arthur, 1893-1960. Jamaican pieces. Jamaican rumba -- Harline, Leigh. Pinocchio. When you wish upon a star; arr.